var quiz_nl = [{
    quiz_id: 1,
    quiz_question: "Wat droegen de begeleiders van de schrijver?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Een hoge hoed",
        option2: "Een zilveren glitterboa",
        option3: "Een prinsessenjurk",
        option4: "Een Star Wars-outfit"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Een zilveren glitterboa"
}, {
    quiz_id: 2,
    quiz_question: "Vanuit welke stad nam de schrijver de trein?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Den Haag",
        option2: "Amsterdam",
        option3: "Utrecht",
        option4: "Leiden"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Den Haag"
}, {
    quiz_id: 3,
    quiz_question: "Welke studie gaat de schrijver doen?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Psychologie",
        option2: "Algemene Sociale Wetenschappen",
        option3: "Communicatiewetenschappen",
        option4: "Rechten"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Algemene Sociale Wetenschappen"
}, {
    quiz_id: 4,
    quiz_question: "Wat gaat de schrijver doen in Utrecht?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Zij gaat vrienden opzoeken die in Utrecht wonen",
        option2: "Zij gaat naar Utrecht om daar te werken",
        option3: "Zij gaat naar Utrecht voor een kennismakingsdag van haar nieuwe studie",
        option4: "Zij gaat een dag winkelen in Utrecht"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Zij gaat naar Utrecht voor een kennismakingsdag van haar nieuwe studie"
}, {
    quiz_id: 5,
    quiz_question: "Hoe heten de begeleiders van de schrijver?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Anne en Yasmin",
        option2: "Anna en Sofia",
        option3: "Sophie en Jasmine",
        option4: "Katie en Lotte"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Anne en Yasmin"
}, {
    quiz_id: 6,
    quiz_question: "Aan welke universiteit gaat de schrijver studeren?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Universiteit van Amsterdam",
        option2: "Universiteit Utrecht",
        option3: "Universiteit Den Haag",
        option4: "Universiteit van Groningen"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Universiteit Utrecht"
}, {
    quiz_id: 7,
    quiz_question: "Hoe stelde de schrijver zich voor?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Anne",
        option2: "Yasmin",
        option3: "Sofia",
        option4: "Juul"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Juul"
}, {
    quiz_id: 8,
    quiz_question: "Wat bevindt zich op het dak van ‘The Basket’?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Een basketbalveld",
        option2: "Een voetbalkooi",
        option3: "Een terras",
        option4: "Een club"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Een basketbalveld"
}];

var quiz_en = [{
    quiz_id: 1,
    quiz_question: "What kind of attribute were the mentors of the author wearing?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "A high hat",
        option2: "A silver, glittery boa",
        option3: "A princess dress",
        option4: "A Star Wars outfit"
    },
    quiz_correct: "A silver, glittery boa"
}, {
    quiz_id: 2,
    quiz_question: "From which city did the author take the train?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "The Hague",
        option2: "Amsterdam",
        option3: "Utrecht",
        option4: "Leiden"
    },
    quiz_correct: "The Hague"
}, {
    quiz_id: 3,
    quiz_question: "Which course of study is the author about to start?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Psychology",
        option2: "Social Sciences",
        option3: "Communication Sciences",
        option4: "Law"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Social Sciences"
}, {
    quiz_id: 4,
    quiz_question: "What is the author going to do in Utrecht?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "She is going to visit friends who live in Utrecht",
        option2: "She is going to Utrecht to work there",
        option3: "She is going to Utrecht for an introductory program of her new study",
        option4: "She is going to go shopping in Utrecht"
    },
    quiz_correct: "She is going to Utrecht for an introductory program of her new study"
}, {
    quiz_id: 5,
    quiz_question: "What are the names of the mentors of the author?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Anne and Yasmin",
        option2: "Anna and Sofia",
        option3: "Sophie and Jasmine",
        option4: "Katie and Lotte"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Anne and Yasmin"
}, {
    quiz_id: 6,
    quiz_question: "At which university is the author going to study?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "University of Amsterdam",
        option2: "Utrecht University",
        option3: "The Hague University",
        option4: "University of Rotterdam"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Utrecht University"
}, {
    quiz_id: 7,
    quiz_question: "How did the author introduce herself?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "Anne",
        option2: "Yasmin",
        option3: "Sofia",
        option4: "Juul"
    },
    quiz_correct: "Juul"
}, {
    quiz_id: 8,
    quiz_question: "What is located at the roof of ‘The Basket’?",
    quiz_options: {
        option1: "A basketball court",
        option2: "A soccer cage",
        option3: "A terrace",
        option4: "A club",
    },
    quiz_correct: "A basketball court"
}];


// var quiz_nl = [{
//     quiz_id: 1,
//     quiz_question: "Wat droegen de begeleiders van de schrijver?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Een plastic kroontje",
//         option2: "Een zilveren glitterboa",
//         option3: "Een zilveren glitterbril",
//         option4: "Een Disneyfiguren-outfit"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Een zilveren glitterboa"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 2,
//     quiz_question: "Vanuit welke stad nam de schrijver de trein?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Den Haag",
//         option2: "Amsterdam",
//         option3: "Utrecht",
//         option4: "Leiden"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Den Haag"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 3,
//     quiz_question: "Welke studie gaat de schrijver doen?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Psychologie",
//         option2: "Algemene Sociale Wetenschappen",
//         option3: "Communicatiewetenschappen",
//         option4: "Rechten"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Algemene Sociale Wetenschappen"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 4,
//     quiz_question: "Waardoor wist de schrijver al waar ‘The Basket’ was?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Omdat zij alvast had willen bekijken waar de ontmoeting was",
//         option2: "Omdat zij in de stad woont en daardoor de plek al kende",
//         option3: "Omdat zij er een wiskundetoets als toelating voor de studie moest maken",
//         option4: "Omdat zij daar een week geleden met een vriend had afgesproken"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Omdat zij er een wiskundetoets als toelating voor de studie moest maken"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 5,
//     quiz_question: "Hoe heten de begeleiders van de schrijver?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Anne en Yasmin",
//         option2: "Anna en Sofia",
//         option3: "Sophie en Jasmine",
//         option4: "Katie en Lotte"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Anne en Yasmin"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 6,
//     quiz_question: "Wanneer was de uitnodiging voor de introductieweek verstuurd?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "5 september",
//         option2: "18 juli",
//         option3: "23 maart",
//         option4: "30 augustus"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "18 juli"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 7,
//     quiz_question: "Hoe stelde de schrijver zich voor?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Anne",
//         option2: "Yasmin",
//         option3: "Sofia",
//         option4: "Juul"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Juul"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 8,
//     quiz_question: "Wat bevindt zich op het dak van ‘The Basket’?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Een basketbalveld",
//         option2: "Een voetbalkooi",
//         option3: "Een terras",
//         option4: "Een club"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Een basketbalveld"
// }];
//
// var quiz_en = [{
//     quiz_id: 1,
//     quiz_question: "What kind of attribute were the mentors of the author wearing?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "A plastic crown",
//         option2: "A silver, glittery boa",
//         option3: "A pair of silver, glittery glasses",
//         option4: "A Disney outfit"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "A silver, glittery boa"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 2,
//     quiz_question: "From which city did the author take the train?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "The Hague",
//         option2: "Amsterdam",
//         option3: "Utrecht",
//         option4: "Leiden"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "The Hague"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 3,
//     quiz_question: "Which course of study is the author about to start?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Psychology",
//         option2: "Social Sciences",
//         option3: "Communication Sciences",
//         option4: "Law"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Social Sciences"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 4,
//     quiz_question: "Why did the author already know where ‘The Basket’ was?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Because she already wanted to see where the meeting was",
//         option2: "Because she is living in Utrecht and was therefore familiar with the place",
//         option3: "Because she had to take an admission exam in mathematics previously near The Basket",
//         option4: "Because last week, she had an appointment at The Basket with a friend"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Because she had to take an admission exam in mathematics previously near The Basket"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 5,
//     quiz_question: "What are the names of the mentors of the author?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Anne and Yasmin",
//         option2: "Anna and Sofia",
//         option3: "Sophie and Jasmine",
//         option4: "Katie and Lotte"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Anne and Yasmin"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 6,
//     quiz_question: "When was the invitation of the introduction week sent?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "5th of September",
//         option2: "18th of July",
//         option3: "23rd of March",
//         option4: "30th of August"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "18th of July"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 7,
//     quiz_question: "How did the author introduce herself?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "Anne",
//         option2: "Yasmin",
//         option3: "Sofia",
//         option4: "Juul"
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "Juul"
// }, {
//     quiz_id: 8,
//     quiz_question: "What is located at the roof of ‘The Basket’?",
//     quiz_options: {
//         option1: "A basketball court",
//         option2: "A soccer cage",
//         option3: "A terrace",
//         option4: "A club",
//     },
//     quiz_correct: "A basketball court"
// }];
